<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mystery>	
 <item>
	<name>Study in Scarlett</name>
	<auth>Sir. Arthur Doyle</auth>
	<description>A Study in Scarlet lays a plot of the astonishing partnership between Sherlock Holmes and Dr. John Watson.</description>
 </item>
 <item>
	<name>The Big Sleep</name>
	<auth>Raymond Chandler</auth>
	<description>Raymond Chandler’s idea of mystery strays from conventions — for him it’s less about the intricate plot and more about the atmosphere and characters.</description>
 </item>
  <item>
	<name>Gone Girl by Gillian Flynn</name>
	<auth>Gillian Flynn</auth>
	<description>Perhaps better known by its major motion picture adaptation, Gone Girl is the ultimate mystery puzzle for the modern media age. Devoted wife Amy’s sudden disappearance throws Nick Dunne into a hailstorm of suspicion — from her parents to his neighbours to the investigators, everyone leans towards believing that he is somehow responsible.</description>
 </item>
   <item>
	<name>The Postman Always Rings Twice</name>
	<auth>James M. Cain</auth>
	<description>The Postman Always Rings Twice is often lauded the most important crime book of the 20th century, and it's not hard to see why. Short, racy, and full of surprises, it will leave you no time to catch your breath. In fact, the language used by Cain was so unprecedentedly explicit, the book was banned in Boston for a while. </description>
 </item>
   <item>
	<name>In Cold Blood by Truman Capote</name>
	<auth>Truman Capote</auth>
	<description>As it’s based on a real-life case that has already been solved, you might think all the mystery is taken out of Truman Capote’s In Cold Blood. Fortunately, that couldn’t be more wrong, because this nonfiction novel is one of the best-selling crime stories of all time. </description>
 </item>
   <item>
	<name>Woman in White</name>
	<auth>Wilkie Collins</auth>
	<description>This Wilkie Collins’s late Victorian novel is among the earliest psychological thrillers ever written. It follows what first appears to be a simple story of two star-crossed lovers — Walter Hartright and Laura Fairlie — who weren’t meant to be together. Laura was betrothed to Sir Percival Glyde and yet she was mysteriously warned not to proceed with the marriage. Meanwhile, the city is gripped by the story of a strange woman clad in white who’s roaming its dark street.</description>
 </item>

</mystery> 